Mute your audio,
but screen share probably, yeah.
This is pull request.
I recently...
Got it, please, and my camera going to be,
ohh, you can you can take the camera off.
That's it's fun to see yourself.
I know the latency, right? Yeah, I mean,
this is literally going up into into
space, yeah, yeah,
that's a little wild too.
Yeah, we are sharing messages.
OK, yeah, so lots of jargon,
lots of jargon,
and for the first first knowledge,
and let's not encrypt our.
Yeah, public communication, exactly right,
and we're trying to as open source as
possible, and so, yeah, and...
Yeah, it becomes inaccessible. Yes, yeah,
I think even I found that,
and what's the easy posters?
What's the is that what it's called?
Better poster for me, yeah,
and just in light of better poster,
it's not that the the people in this
industry know know the jargon,
it's that we all kind of...
struggle through it every time,
figure it out a lot of the time.
And I think it's not that we're all
totally fluent in this jargon,
so that we all kind of try to figure it
out.
And just the point that the simpler we
make it isn't just for people who have no
experience in this field,
but also for people who
Have a lot of experience in the field.
It's also simpler for them,
so let's make it better for everybody.
Yeah, and yeah, so I think,
and I think it's just like a ask through
Claude again, like, OK,
remove the jargon and make this better.
OK, that's a fine way to do that. Yeah,
and I might like,
and at some point go line by line through
and stuff,
but I think that's a fine Claude thing to
do, yeah.
And then I have a couple of notes,
so I can put that in the add,
just in a comment,
you're gonna take these out, I think.
And Kelly,
we were talking about the CAD stuff and
going from then.
This can get us like 8% of the way. Yeah,
pretty, pretty solid paper.
I think I can go line by line after that
and then make it really good paper. Yeah,
I think that's a good way to do it, and...
Also, just for this meeting, I said,
we just kind of go through my notes and
then right and hear what you think about
it. Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's great. Yeah,
go ahead. Yeah, so, yeah, jargon,
and then I'll just go through line by
line once it gets to a little bit of a
better spot. Okay, okay,
and the rest of this...
Is about graphs and graphics, so.
If we go,
so there's two places where we have
graphics right now.
There's the graphs we already have in
here. So we're pretty okay,
we can get better ones,
and then we're just kind of like, this,
yeah, missing stuff. Or like,
why do we have the timeline in it?
We don't need that. Yeah, that's okay.
We can take that out.
I think I had mentioned the timeline at
one point, just from a...
Sort of a passing comment, like...
What would probably be more useful is
like number of things as a function of
time, not just, yeah, yeah, a random.
That went with a couple words.
Like,
if we're if we're talking about the
generative CAD piece, maybe it's OK.
We can throw whatever we want into
supplementary information. That's true.
That's one that I'd be totally fine,
just gonna, yeah,
just throw in supplementary, not that one,
but more like...
Yeah, so Jen AI usage as a function of,
yeah, of time.
I think it's cool that we have that data.
I think we should use it. That's awesome.
I I run it for a couple projects, so yeah,
alright, no, no, yeah, keep going,
keep going. That's cool, I like that.
Usually, a few $1000 per project,
if you were to charge an API rate for
them, and yeah,
and so some of these are helpful,
I just presently seeing what it has and
saying, "OK,
what do I think could actually be helpful?
What would be what would be supplementary
and what, yeah, yeah, like this,
like showing the the...
Like, how it looks at forty-five degrees?
Like,
people know what forty-five degrees is.
I know, yeah, that would be OK,
but I did think we might be helpful, like,
put a coordinate frame on the jar,
something like that,
so people know what axes we're talking
about. OK, that's sort of sure,
just like somebody seems to be combined
and stuff, same thing here.
And like a cross-section is good,
but like this isn't super helpful,
and that's an issue.
Were we trying to talk about the tap
caller?
Like the Janie I part of the top column,
not sure, yeah, okay,
I need to go back to, yeah,
I can figure it out more, and then here,
that was the one, yeah, yeah,
that's where it's actually, yeah,
I need a couple of case studies, like,
and they they walk you through this one
of like, this is how we,
this is just showcasing the kind of the
design problems, yeah,
and that's helpful that we can keep some
of those.
Yeah, and then this is fake data. OK,
which is awesome, so...
Yeah, I guess we hadn't pinged it yet,
saying put in real data, yeah,
so this is still from from back when,
before we had it, yeah,
and then I asked it to make some graphs
based on real data, so now we have, ohh,
so that's in, ohh, that is in the, OK,
I just missed it, so, so we have...
Yeah, so resource,
so we have graphics in two places.
We have the stuff that it put already put
into the paper, yeah,
which is like mostly pictures and stuff
that are legitimate, and then big data,
yeah,
and I thought it did a good job like this,
'cause I asked it, I asked it to put, yes,
yeah, I like the the the.
And then, and then these are the paper,
the things that I brought up.
And this is most of what I want to talk
about, I think,
making a kind of know what to do,
editing the other one,
like the actual text,
and those graphics and stuff.
Then,
this is just the first pass of the graph,
yeah, and a couple of things, um,
of working thoughts, Luke, um.
So, we let we talked about how, like,
we the main way that we interface with
the pattern is through Claude, right? Now,
to me, it's like sometimes scary,
and I'm not sure about that.
One thing I ran into with this,
the notice is I think it's been super
handy to have just, you know,
say Claude run this and record this data
and record the data,
even when I thought I was doing a good
job of like...
Following up and knowing what it was
recording and stuff, I don't,
now that I'm trying to write a paper and
thinking like, well,
what graphs would be helpful? I'm like,
I don't even know what metrics we're
using. What do we even collect? Yeah,
what do we even do? So, yeah,
there's another interesting thing,
like it's the same like diameter of the
auger problem, right?
It's like I should have,
this should be second nature and I have
no idea what we're talking about.
I think we even, at some point,
I don't remember if it made it into a lot
of the recent problems,
at some point we were saying.
Like, okay,
what data needs to be collected for the
placeholder figures that we, yes, yeah,
yeah, noodle, like that we thought about,
yeah, what would actually go in there?
That's what you need to do to get the
data for the,
but at some point there may have been a
disconnect, yeah.
It became collect the data,
like make sure you're collecting the data
for that paper,
and that you're showing lots of this of
data getting added, yeah, in line,
so we can spot check it as it goes, yeah,
so yeah, I think I can understand that,
yeah.
Just funny, I don't know. Wait,
what data did we collect? Yeah,
when I was thinking, like,
if we get to have, yeah,
just when I was coming up with, like,
I got somebody to put this away and I was
like, "Hey, just thinking from your head,
what graphs would be helpful?" Yeah,
and it was hard to think of them,
because I was like, "What even,
what are the metrics that we even,
that would even be helpful with this
stuff?" Yeah.
Yeah, so that said,
some of these are really good,
some of these are really confusing,
and there's a lot of jargon here as well,
and it's difficult, like feed factor,
and it throws around,
and it's been using this dose rate, right?
Like, that's our, yeah,
like dose rate is probably what we put in,
right? Yeah, 'cause it's a powdered doser.
It is, it is, it's a bad one.
I think it's a fair, yeah, and has,
you know what this is,
where revolution RSD,
you know what that it stands for,
root mean squared, root squared deviation.
OK, yeah, basically,
it felt like it's saying a scatter, but...
Yeah,
but it's just like this is not a good use,
that's not a good use, an arrow, yeah,
and anyways,
so it's you use a lot of jargon and
that's even to me who's been doing
private, yeah, for a lot, so, yeah, so...
This was interesting too. It's like,
I'm pretty sure it was saying nothing was
dispensed. Yes, yeah, get it,
but like that's not really a helpful way
to say that, right? Like,
don't put it on the graph,
then it has like, yeah,
just make a note and or show it as like.
Hatched, like a hatched bar, like, yes,
like, yeah, so strike through the text,
yes, yeah,
these just seem to need a lot of work in
order to be kind of readable, yeah,
and so, yeah,
and this is at least the data,
it is the data, it does have the data.
And then this is, so that's good. Okay,
food safe versus, yeah,
the ones more research relevant.
10 milligrams per revolution of the auger
when it's at 45 degrees.
Not considering the fill level,
which I think we said was.
Like the fill level does affect,
so probably not for a fixed fill level on
this one. Yeah.
But then we can go from 10 milligrams per
revolution for sodium thalzonate all the
way up to 230 that I actually didn't
realize that the ALSI 10MG would be the
highest flowing of everything.
But it's not that different from.
Zanthem found me. This is a watch, yeah,
yeah. Ohh, wait.
Isn't this the absolute value of 146?
Yeah, 10100, so yeah, it's like...
Yeah,
but a lot of a lot of them are just
within.
Some percentage of each other,
except for these. Yeah, what was CMC like?
Was also kind of flowery or...
This one, I mean,
let me look back over with Carl's videos.
I have the video of me, oh yeah, yeah.
Or rather, I have, I,
I have some YouTube videos where I just
had them in a cup, like a transparent,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
that it felt like gave me a better,
pretty tangible sentence, yeah,
of the pattern, yeah,
it was helpful to like, you know, like,
pull it out on the spoons, like, on the,
yeah, yeah, yeah, this one is like,
is this tall, this one is this tall.
Yeah, that sounds, and so saying.
So, I guess I want to know which, which,
we'll go through all these and I want to
know which ones you think are helpful,
and like I,
and then I can clean it up and make it
more readable. Yeah, put them in,
or which ones you think about what we're
missing.
I think this one A2 right here is...
has good information in it that we can
display graphically.
I think the use of color to split the
food safe surrogate versus the research
relevant ones is good.
We want to keep a visual separation
between the different types.
And.
We shouldn't be plotting any data for the
silicon, the brown rice,
the negative 325 mesh,
the brown rice flour, the feed silica.
And.
Like,
we can optionally keep it on the graph,
but just like a strike through,
a strike through here. Yeah,
I think just like a strike through of
text would come across fine,
and then I think we really do need to
clarify in the caption which thought was
putting the caption as embedded text.
Every figure, yeah,
no matter how many times it has to keep
it out of the figure. I get it. I get it.
Yeah, it's like, yeah, oh,
it's all in one file. Yeah, helpful,
but not, yeah, yeah, having in there like.
Clarifications about.
other factors that affect things like the
fill level.
The words.
Controlled for here.
But the raw data is available, yeah.
And that might be where the Claude team
as well go through and grab.
these data points,
what was the fill level when this was
collected?
I also don't know if repeats were run on
this. It seems like maybe not.
It's not an identical repeat of 45 degree
tilts.
Yeah, yeah, so maybe, maybe that's it.
We can just try to get the data for what
the fill levels were and see if there's...
We should address that somehow,
and just be in the caption, yeah,
and it was at the full level.
I think it's going to be hard to measure.
I didn't really control for that myself.
It was enough like up to pretty close to
the top,
but it was like totally at the top.
And some of them didn't have enough
powder,
so they're like kind of half like half.
Oh, yeah.
So it kind of varies throughout it.
And yeah. That makes sense.
So I should have done that, but...
Did we,
did you weigh the ****** before and after?
No, okay, that was fine. No, I didn't,
once I was done, it was like,
that would be a good idea. Yeah, okay,
that was a good idea. Okay,
and on that one.
We'll see what it comes back with if it
notices something.
Strange, but.
Nothing here really seems.
Concerning.
These ones were really hard to get things
out of.
These ones all fall in kind of a similar
range. Yeah.
These ones were really difficult to get
anything out of. Also,
this team silica is weird.
Just don't touch it. Yeah, just don't.
Not gonna work.
This one probably has something to do
with it being really jagged.
Yeah.
Yeah, I bet, yeah.
Frankly,
the ALSI 10MG probably flows so well in
part because they are.
particles for laser powder fusion,
which requires very high sphericity. Yeah,
they're very spherical,
uniform size distribution.
So you have to use them in the metal 3D
printing. So that in retrospect,
it's like, okay, yeah, that makes sense.
I'm a little surprised.
I didn't think the silicon.
Generally looks.
Very spherical, but for whatever reason,
I guess the silicon is fine, fine,
so we could we can make some comment,
we could have some commentary about this.
Yeah,
those are kind of the main things that
jump out to me.
And.
Maybe keep on.
Yeah, this one.
This one is, it looks,
it looks helpful if I really look at it
for, yeah,
letting it do the better way to do this,
but, and it's kind of the same.
Oh, this is the lateral scatter,
is that right? Or no? Not sure,
but I don't know how we would find that
other than like with the camera or
something. Like, that's what I'm like,
I don't even know what we're talking
about here. But I like, I like,
I like having like really does,
like I like that distinction here.
I like the way it's set up.
But, and revolution are still.
This percent block C,
it keeps saying about these blocks.
I think you had a sense of what that was,
yeah, as I never went back to the test.
That was the other thing I was realizing
was like,
"I'm not sure where all the blocks are,
yeah, so it's just the test that I had,
so I had to like make it make it a test,
like a script of a bunch of tests, yeah.
So, the block is a different test, yeah,
and that, but I, I don't know, like,
obviously in my head,
what each of them are, yeah, and so,
and yeah, I was gonna have actually,
I wrote them,
but that would be a good table to have,
like, yeah, exactly, so...
They're better, it's like test protocols,
yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah, but sorry,
maybe we come back to that,
and then I think I like the idea of this
graph,
and he's trying to say I like the way
that it says it visually, yeah,
and what the heck is the way, yeah, so,
and we'll see, I don't know,
I'll mess with it, and...
Yeah, RSD might mean something else.
That's the thing too, right? Thank you,
right, 'cause it's done so many,
like it produces so much content with
every yesterday and stuff. Yeah,
it's the it feels like, oh,
we've been using this this terminology
for the last like 3 weeks, and it's like,
well,
I probably should have read it more
closely, I guess,
but I don't know what you're talking
about, and yeah, yeah,
we can go look at this one.
And.
And then this one I like,
I need to look again at the specific at
the block or whatever,
at what it was running,
but I like the idea of like we were
shooting for, like this is the error.
Yeah,
based on the same test for all the
encounters and that's it is somewhat of
like a control problem now that.
Right, problem, yeah,
and we'll just point to like...
We used a simple method in future work.
We're going to do super cool calibration
stuff. Yeah.
Yeah.
And another thing like these, like these,
these are all,
this is not any kind of range,
so this should all just be aligned
perfectly, right? Like,
so that that's a specific type of plot
that's...
It's jitter, like in matplotlib,
like these plotting libraries,
it's called jitter.
And that's useful when you have a lot of
data points and you want to show a
distribution. Yeah.
Without doing a violin plot that like,
wipes things out and without having a
bunch of overlapping points. I see.
We do not need a jitter.
For 3 points, yeah, for three points,
that makes sense, so...
Nice, but yeah, yeah,
not sure what you're trying to do, yeah,
and then this one, and I also like, again,
I'm not really sure what it's trying to
say,
and time determining the dose feeding,
and as far as I know,
like it stopped the dose and then time
for it to just stop dispensing anything,
so like...
Okay.
And...
I, but they're not sure what the taps are.
Block G and the blocks seem really
important because it's yeah.
So, 3 doses of 1 gram per powder,
each markers 1 dose,
gray rule spins the three, buggy,
I think is the one actually.
I could just zoom in, open that one, yeah.
Annotations means solenoid taps.
So we can rice flour.
Like these ones, again,
like they didn't do anything,
like it never, yeah,
it's why are they on here? Yeah,
it's like technically there was measured
data, but it's noise, yeah.
And,
and displaying it this way isn't helpful,
yeah.
And also, please don't mind up to me.
Yeah.
Yeah, they like bad green though,
green is OK, yellow is overshoot,
red is stalled.
So, I don't know,
I like the idea of some of these, like,
I like the idea of, okay,
when I stopped it,
how much time did it take to stop?
And maybe that's a helpful metric,
but is that what it's talking about?
I don't know, that's the thing.
Time to terminate the dose,
they can do well.
This is just like how long it took to get
there.
Like, we're trying to do 1 gram. I think,
I think Block G is the one that took the
took the longest. I think it's yeah,
3 doses of 1 gram,
so it's trying to get to 1 gram,
so this is how long it took.
I I'm thinking this up a little bit too,
so it took a long time to dose CMC, yeah,
and we...
Didn't get to, I guess, sir,
I didn't get there.
So I guess that's another thing.
We got the revolutions at the 45 degrees,
but also when we ran the same.
How accurate,
so it's it's maybe maybe this is part of
it and we're.
Maybe there's a way we can represent.
either all in one or separately,
this idea of here was the unique counter
type.
Mm.
And it's food safe or...
Uh, like our research relevant one.
Here are the ones that float fast.
Here are the ones we were able to get,
like,
here's the accuracy when we try to be
accurate with this powder.
Under some.
Three-phase test procedure,
whatever we ended up using for that.
And...
Alright.
What's the other one we're just talking
about? Like the time,
the total time it takes to get to that.
Point,
which is basically just the function of
the dose rate in a lot of ways.
And what didn't flow well and why didn't
it flow well? It's kind of a...
We can, we have some SEM images of.
The powders, throw those in, keep it like,
hey, and there's us.
Just some characterization data on some
of this.
So many graphs that show all that stuff.
Yeah, so either it depends a little bit.
I don't know how well we could try to
show that all in one graph. Yeah.
Or we try to do a panel or we just keep
them separate graphs and I'd be okay with.
Part of it is that.
In while we were talking and we're
looking at.
This one and it was like CMC.
Obviously took a while to get there and
it stalled which I...
Assume means that there came a point
where it stopped dispensing anything.
I'm not sure where.
Sure why it would do that. Yeah.
And then the question becomes, well,
what was the target?
And those.
And how close did it get there? Yeah,
like, we're kind of missing, yeah,
that's this one is the, ohh, yeah, yeah,
so that,
how do you like how close they got,
so they even got close, not awesome,
and that, OK,
so that's what the thing by stalls, like,
we did get, yeah, we got somewhere.
That's right, but then it's like,
I don't know why I would why I would stop
there.
I think it's back to the field phase
thing, like it can't go back to phases,
like once it gets to the tab,
then it's just gonna keep tapping and,
totally, yeah,
just have that little pocket in the front,
yeah, it just keeps tapping, so, like,
why, like CMC here has,
you're catching like they had 140, yeah,
yeah.
150 tabs, yeah,
and still didn't get there, so...
But again, that's the controls thing,
right? Let's just have you, yeah, yeah,
and so I think it's still meaningful to
have this heuristic test and data from
that, just like...
Yeah, if we take this heuristic,
people want to know the performance of it.
Yeah.
And so even though we're sectioning off
more advanced things for Will.
People will read this paper and they want
it like, so can you,
can you just have batteries?
Can you just have batteries?
How fast can you do it? Yeah, yeah,
can you be accurate? Like, yeah.
And it's helping for me to remind myself
that it's not just,
we're looking for graphs that showcase
the powder dose of the powers, right?
This is, yeah,
we're not sure what CMC does or something,
yeah, they're trying to show the powder,
so yeah.
Yeah, sweet.
I'm talking a little too much. Thank you.
I think this is the last one, yeah. Ohh,
yeah, so then it's really helpful,
I think, and just it's cool to see how,
like, OK,
so it's an auger and it's spinning and it
falls out and it falls out,
so this is like...
Yeah, yeah,
I do like that as soon as burst,
and this is how you can see how the
powder it's got.
Yeah, like that, and yeah,
'cause every everyone is like a...
Never really, it's continuous, right?
Yeah, stream,
even as continuous as we're trying to get,
yeah, even with even with this one,
probably the most continuous, yeah, yeah,
still not.
Yeah, I like that one. I like C2. Yeah.
Apparently.
This is in the supplementary information.
That seems like a pretty good one for the
name.
But here we've got...
Protocol A.
We'll stop using block protocol A.
Nothing was varied.
It's a balanced baseline.
So we have the tilt at 45, we do 8 reads.
And, okay, gotcha. So.
It's trying to get the noise floor.
The static hold, so 04590,
hold for 15 seconds, but no actuation.
So just looking at gravity.
Okay, eight trials for this,
three trials for protocol B.
These are two,
like if you're holding for 15 seconds at
a time,
but you're not like instancing between
them.
Is that a call? Yeah,
I think it's just like,
if you just hold it there, yeah, I mean,
you just hold it there,
but it says like it does three trials,
yeah, or I guess 'cause it's 04590.
Oh, maybe. Yeah,
I don't know if it's three trials.
It might be something where it's like it.
Goes back to its normal thing,
and then it goes back up to forty-five,
and then, yeah, that's a good question,
yeah,
so to figure out what the best test
server, hey, we run the test server, yeah,
rotation yield,
so this is the zero forty-five 90.
6 revolutions, 30 RPM.
Yeah, just... Oh, okay.
Revolution to revolution spread.
Beat factor and precision at each tilt,
so from...
Like for the first revolution,
this is how much mass was delivered.
For the second revolution,
this is how much mass was delivered.
I think is where if you go up a little
bit.
This one, I think that's this YX list.
Maybe.
Block scene? Yeah, so this is block.
But the revolution to revolution spread,
that seems to be what it's trying to
capture there, but that doesn't.
I guess how much the variance there is
between. I'd rather just see error bars.
I'd rather just see error bars on that.
Yeah. Or the,
actually the individual data points,
maybe. Looks like 18 trials for this one.
Again,
we really need to figure out what that.
Ohh.
What does a trial mean? Yeah, yeah,
rephrase. Yeah, speed sweep, so 15 RPM,
45 RPM, 90 RPM, tilt at 45, 3 revolutions,
streaming the balance,
so mass flow rate versus rotation speed.
Within revolution pulsation of the
discharge from the streamed mass trace.
Pulsation.
the discharge problem.
Is that the pulse? Maybe we go down to...
On block D streaming balance polls during
three revolutions at 15 RPM.
So, there's a 15 points, yeah,
I guess it's just saying that...
It noticed kind of the pulsating user,
as I don't know why I picked these for
powder specifically, yeah, yeah,
tap yield.
So till 0 and 45, 8 trials.
And then...
Doing A refeed,
so I guess just like doing a revolution,
because tapping, yeah, removes that, yeah,
yeah, okay, so 360 rotation,
one solenoid tap,
and then a 60 millisecond tap, is that?
Wait, 60 milliseconds on.
I guess you send a signal to the...
Yeah,
I guess we just turn our current on in
the solenoid for some time and then drop
it so I guess it's a 60 millisecond pulse.
Okay, yeah, so it turns on, like it hits,
and 60 seconds later, 60 seconds later.
I think so, yeah. Sure. I guess, yeah,
that's one of those other things, like,
oh yeah.
Yeah, I guess that again chose, yeah,
so 60 millisecond pulses, just one tap.
Yeah, and that refeed locks separately,
32 trials.
Obviously, nothing, yeah.
Yeah, I still want to get.
that back on at some point, but yeah,
it's not. Okay.
Priorities, we have, we have,
we have priorities right now, yeah,
closed loop dose, 3 doses, 1 gram target,
three phase controller, yeah,
and so mass dose error, time to dose.
The breakdown of bulk find and tap the
controller,
and so that's where we go back up.
Here, 3 doses, and this says trials,
3 doses, so maybe trials.
the generous interpretation of trials.
Like it ran this procedure.
18 times per pattern. Yeah.
Which in this case would have been,
what is this, I guess, 32 revolutions?
But that seems like a lot.
But like for C,
like it's 6 revolutions at 0.4590 each,
so that's 18. Oh, total. Yeah,
I think that's what, yeah.
That sounds.
Right.
So, the less generous interpretation,
yeah, yeah, yes, the lazy,
the lazy version of, yes, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, so from that information,
do you think there's anything that we're
really lacking? A predo front of...
Wait, hold up. Uh,
it's not related for your friend.
so much, but just a scatter plot of...
Dose error versus time to dose or.
Or no, do we have that already? Is that?
You go up a little bit, is that this one?
Ohh, no, that doesn't have time to dose,
so basically this plot,
but with time to dose, same with these,
and so we would have...
not an access for the powders we would
have.
Unique symbols, I guess, or yeah,
like some way to different, yeah,
within the the chart itself,
so this would be like dose error versus
time to dose,
and that would only pull from G.
Yep.
Yeah, OK, yes.
Move the table of move that table onto
the main thing. Yeah,
I think we could have.
Like we kind of want to capture the
effect of each.
Isolated.
And so, we got we got tilt, speed,
and tapping,
and isolate the effects of those two,
or try to say, like...
Oh.
Yeah, do we have something that's like...
One tap for this powder typically gives
this much. And here's the spread.
Do we already have something like that?
Ohh, what's all this? I don't know.
Was that the supplementary drop-down,
or maybe I just I started typing and then
it popped up?
Is it summarize the, yeah, it's been.
Yeah.
Oh yeah, that's right.
We only did it for one mass.
I figured if we talked about that one,
I'm doing it for a couple different
target.
Basses.
Does that sound familiar? Okay.
Like, they're trying to go to, like...
It's like 20 milligrams, 1 gram, 5 grams.
It's like the target dose, but that might,
that's more like Will's, yeah,
we may have just like sectioning that out,
they, yeah.
When you can do the test,
it just told called the mid test,
then seemed helpful, yeah, yeah, but...
No, you cannot compute the CV from n = 1.
Thank you.
Well, condescending.
Like, it's often insulting. It's like,
were you trying to insult my intelligence?
There's.
Where are you looking?
And.
Oh yeah, maybe just to know,
like I think for the ones that didn't
dispense, it's a question of, well,
maybe we need to look at the auger
geometry.
Because if we had an empty cylinder.
We would expect some powder to flow if we
tilt it at 90 degrees and spin it and tap
it.
So that one becomes more of a like a
design thing. Yeah.
Oh yeah,
so I had had a follow-up at one point.
Oh, yeah, so this, for example.
We have a...
Yeah, milligrams per solenoid tap.
and the feed factor at 45.
And...
Which I guess is just saying, like...
Things that.
Feed at approximately the same rate with
revolutions can have a dramatically
different.
A tap response.
I guess that's what we kind of get from,
yeah, from the...
And then maybe going through some of
these other figures for the first time at
least.
Yeah, if I do a screen share.
Grant.
And you can look on here, just.
Summarize the totality of the data that's
been collected.
Evaluating effects of different
parameters on the semi-instantaneous dose
rate, do EDA,
it's not to rate data analysis.
Oh,
about 64 grams of powder moved through
the auger in the characterization blocks,
and another 22 grams of doses.
Everything.
The.
OK, 19 runs.
Fiction powders, 1200 measured trials.
That's pretty good. That's cool.
That's pretty cool.
A little more than that for the streamed
balance polls, like individual, like,
here's the balance. 36 closed loop doses.
Oh, pet my ego. So clean.
Your question of tell me where the data
set is? Yeah, because it's like,
or my point about,
I guess it's referring to,
that doesn't involve complex optimization.
Yeah.
Ohh, what do you know?
This is not optimization. What? Yeah, uh,
right, so this is just giving me the...
Dave.
Okay, yes, thank you. Thank you.
vibration matter.
Oh, AB.
Ohh,
this is just showing how many trials were
run,
so it's basically saying we got all the
data, except for G doesn't have,
we don't have G for salt, sodium sulfate,
the silicon, fume silica, barium chloride,
or the ALSI 10.
I shouldn't remember who that was.
I think it was because of the...
And few moves causing a bunch of
migrations and things,
and so just had to pause in that, so...
If we were to go back and collect some
more data,
filling in these ones would be the only,
like, a completeness, yeah,
step by the manuscript.
A...
What do you think about that? Like,
you know, redoing this? Yeah, the the.
The three-phase dose, yeah,
test for the other ones.
Does that seem like they could be over,
I don't remember why it didn't happen,
but I can't imagine that I didn't do it,
but well, I mean,
out of literally 1200 measured trials,
sure, but I think you...
Like,
we still just have the augers that are
filled. I mean,
is it easier to just clean up? Yeah, OK.
OK, gotcha.
Um,
it's still in the few minutes and stuff,
so thank you for turning on the scale.
Do you know why it turned on? No,
I'm gonna if it's turned off at no time
today, not not great, yeah, and...
Yeah,
and if like that would be fine if Claude
could like send a ping and make it up,
but yeah.
Is it expected that the scale would turn
off after some period of time?
Sam mentioned that there was no real
indication as to why it was off.
Yes, I can rerun those. Yeah, those week.
That's interesting too.
It's like how much was dosed?
Like in total 9 grams of the ALSI 10MG
kind of stuff, yeah,
because these tests weren't at like a
threshold of, yeah, dose as much,
just see how much gets dosed. OK,
the rate.
Mean dose rate at the reference condition.
milligrams per second.
And is it saying?
That's so strange.
Dose rate spans 3 decades under one
frozen parameter set block,
or under one frozen parameter set,
block C.
30 RPM, tilt 45 degrees,
mean of 6 single revolutions.
So I think it's saying...
Just right.
Ohh, no, I was just saying, for...
It's including this as one of the decades,
one of the orders of magnitude,
but just that it can vary based on.
Okay, with revolutions specifically.
Tilt.
Zero 4590 mass per auger revolution.
So yeah, this is saying.
In general.
90 degree tilt.
gives more dispensed mess.
How much of the flow is gravity,
not the auger? Okay,
that's actually interesting.
Gravity assist.
Wait, ohh, no, I guess it.
For some of these, if you put it at 90.
It wouldn't just start flowing. Yeah.
And none of that,
that's something very close.
It takes a long time to stop. Okay.
But they do stop. Okay. So gravity assist,
which really I think is just repeated
this data,
is that when you put sodium alginate.
At 90 degrees,
it dispenses 15 times faster than when
it's at 0.
This shouldn't even be on there.
Game Silica and CMC.
Is there any Game Silica is 2.
2 times faster than it came out?
Because I think it was probably because
it was measuring the noise floor on scale
and happened to be greater than one.
I don't know.
Uh...
The one was tilt.
I'm just looking at Silicon 325,
and there's nothing in 045,
but it's saying I got something.
It conveys a little bit degrees. Sorry,
go ahead.
That was one of the ones,
so that's this one here, and...
This one right here. Oh, for taps. Okay.
Okay, apps.
Okay, so it sounds like the silicon, yeah,
I mean that's kind of an interesting,
yeah, things like, hey,
we couldn't get any of this out when it
was, unless we tilted it,
so that's kind of...
I guess kind of the flip side of things
is...
Ohh.
Is there something that wouldn't work at
90 degrees that would work at a, right?
Is that, yeah, makes sense, like,
that's a story, yeah, that's a story,
right?
It's saying the ones that need gravity
are cohesive ones.
Oh, okay.
I'm seeing that a little bit here.
So for at least...
or white rice flour.
Keeping in mind this is log scale.
you're getting.
Or?
Yeah. Does it? Yeah.
It has a bigger effect in terms of
relative percent, yeah,
than it does on these ones,
though magnitude.
I'm sure these ones are still...
More, absolutely. Yeah.
Hey, speed. Oh. Wow, the most,
the very most.
I thought there was another one that said.
..
Okay.
Maybe it was something different, nice,
yeah.
OK.
Six times the speed buys about three
times the rate.
Ohh, it it did do different speeds, right?
I guess so, yeah,
but it did the 1535 and 90 that's right
for RPM, yeah, so dose rate.
Ohh, very interesting. Yeah,
spinning it faster. You know,
the most interesting thing about the data
is that you, if you spin it faster,
that's not looking so good,
but that's the most interesting thing.
Yeah, it's not awesome. Yeah.
There we go.
I feel like that's a subtle dig. Yeah, no.
Yeah.
The.
It will change your...
If you think of Claude as a cynical robot
that's kind of like sarcastic and salty
towards you and very lazy, like, oh, okay,
human, I don't want to do that.
It totally changes how you read things,
or at least it did for me a year ago.
It's like, oh, I'm so sorry.
Yeah, I slaved for hours on this thing.
It's like, you ran for 20 minutes.
What do you mean? That's funny.
Everything about it's probably good for
my like communication skills that I've
been trying to be like, okay,
so I need to tell it exactly like,
say it really, yeah, yeah,
exactly what I do, like it,
like if I just communicate with people,
it'll probably be good for me to just
like...
Think, okay, how do I, like,
there is no way to misunderstand what I'm
saying here, you gotta be really clear.
Yeah, I think it's something.
Okay, flights filled by time.
Mass per revolution.
relative to 15 RPM.
Is that...
These ones.
Hill.
So, when it said 15, they all like...
And when the 45 is how much different
they dispense versus 15.
Mm-hmm, that's in the bottom one,
so I didn't know, but wait, like,
is it saying these ones dispensed less?
Yeah, I think so, at higher speeds, like,
ohh, by time, not by turn, okay, okay,
so do it, so, ohh, ohh, meaning it was,
it was,
because it's per resolution seconds, not.
So, like,
you're dispensing less mass per
revolution for these ones at 90 RPM,
but you're doing more revolutions in the
same amount of time, so you're doing OK.
Six times the number of revolutions,
but each revolution is only getting,
you know, 50% of what the other ones were.
OK.
Sure, sure. Yeah.
And then it's calling that as regimes.
And it's choosing to say we have fill
limited versus mobilization limited.
Okay, okay.
Fill limited, mobilization limited.
So I guess it's,
so the blue ones are saying,
I think those are fill limited.
So like everything below is fill limited,
everything above is mobilization limited.
So if it's below,
it just doesn't have time to bounce
around and get to the front. Like you're..
. Oh, like the auger's moving faster,
but it's not kind of reaching it yet.
Yeah, like you don't have enough, yeah,
you don't have enough friction or gravity.
It didn't...
It didn't.
I'm not sure what the...
Tilt was for this.
I understand.
R for A English voice.
Yeah, that seems.
I guess it doesn't matter either way in
terms of, yeah, that,
but I guess some fill.
Versus motivation,
I guess that does tell you something
about, yeah, the powders like visually,
like what's happening in, yeah,
inside of that, yeah,
like it's just going so fast that it
can't, yeah, keep up.
K.
Faster rotation mobilizes powder rather
than starving, but so I, okay,
maybe where because it's cohesive,
you have these bigger chunks and globs
that get rattled the rattles and through,
yeah.
Uh, let me see.
And some of those could probably factor
into Will's work with the optimization.
Like, oh,
maybe we have ways of describing powders
that can help us learn more about the
characteristics of the powders. Yeah,
because I see what that was before I was
asking if there was like a Reynolds
number for, yeah, for powders and said no,
so that's not great for us.
And it's, and yeah, I don't like this,
this is the current tradition that we can
use, yeah.
the fact that you could change the speed
of the auger.
And maybe be able to tell whether or not
it's a cohesive powder. Yeah,
like that's kind of a cool.
I think so we could probably make note of
that in the paper.
Going into future work,
like this data can also tell us things
about the powder. For example,
we notice the difference in, like,
we're by changing the revolution speed.
We're able to distinguish between
cohesive and non-cohesive powders.
Yeah, I...
That could be kind of a good feature work,
yeah, call out.
Depletion control. OK,
this is this is good.
So block C,
6 consecutive revolutions at fixed
conditions,
mass declines by median 1% per revolution.
So, in this 30 to 50% decline.
Or actually, wait,
basically this is the fill level.
Like it was looking at.
The effect of fill level, yeah, over time,
it's like, not entirely fill level, maybe,
but probably mostly fill level,
as a scheme jumping, yeah,
semi-instantaneous rate,
one slug per revolution.
The delivers one slug. One slug.
I think it's just like that. Okay.
Yeah, sure, sure.
Block D streamed balance poles tilt 45
degrees, top row is 15 RPM,
and top row dotted lines mark revolutions,
dotted lines. Oh, okay,
so let me correct you.
So,
Revolution One took about four seconds.
OK, so it's about four seconds per.
Revolution 15 RPM.
Uh, 15 * 4.
Uhh...
And then what's going on down here?
Discharge locks to the revolution,
median autocorrelation peak at 4 seconds,
pulsation is real at 15 RPM,
but 45 and 90 RPM are under sampled.
So these are just the same ones,
cumulative mass.
I think it's good that it shows the, yeah,
that's nice that it shows the revolution
and the.
So you could just show the revolution,
but maybe it's kind of useful,
but then I'm okay with that.
It's kind of like a...
Visualization aid, so you can clearly see.
each of these. Now what, here's something.
NACL.
Not much until we hit,
maybe I'm reading into it too much, but...
Not much accumulating until we've already
done a full revolution.
Yeah, it's like leading edge versus, yeah,
trailing edge a little bit. It's like,
for this one, OK,
same thing here for Xanthem Gum,
which that one.
I thought flows so well, so smoothly,
like, yeah,
before the first revolution is even
complete, we have something, yeah,
that's like,
is it just where it happened to be? Yeah,
that's what I was, yeah.
You can't guarantee they'll start at the
exact same place, yeah,
with the exact distribution of patterns
based on the previous dosing runs that
you ran, so that is.
Get tricky with how do you reset an
experiment? Yeah, what's a reset?
But also when you're actually dosing,
you're not going to reset every time.
So how do you?
Consider where you, where, yeah,
like the current state of the of the
system.
Discharge locks to the revolution.
Autocorrelation of the semi-instantaneous
rate, and I think that's just...
Pointing out what we talked about here of
the time period, I think it's cyclical,
OK, with...
So, I guess, like, right here, like...
There's a repeating pattern within each
of these that corresponds to that.
I wonder if part of that is the...
timing, like if we ran it at one RPM.
And I guess maybe this, yeah,
buttons out because the powder is kind of
settling. Like,
I wonder how much of this is kind of the
powder bouncing. Yeah,
I wonder if we get like a stronger
reverberation better,
that would help with this too. Yeah, yeah.
It was going constantly there.
pulsation at 15 RPM, crest factor.
95th percent rate over the mean rate.
15.
Chris.
Okay.
Crest Factor.
95th percent instantaneous rate divided
by the mean.
That percentile.
I need this percent.
Instantaneous.
Uh, yeah,
it's trying to do some fancy signal
processing, okay?
Crest vector, OK.
The ratio of a waveform's peak amplitude
to its root mean square value.
showing how extreme or spiky the peaks
are.
OK, Spike.
All right, so some measure, like,
I'll speculators.
I don't think we really hear about that.
Every knob on one axis, okay.
Uhh...
Maybe this goes to say,
let's not put everything on one axis.
Yeah. Maybe that is.
Or at least not in this way.
He's like, I get it what it's saying,
what it's saying. One revolution at zero.
One revolution at 45,
one revolution at 90.
One.
Where the, yeah, like, yeah,
like it's missing, yeah.
Ling got.
That's confusing, yeah.
So I kind of get it, but also it's...
I think I'm pretty confident on let's not.
Have this kind of totality graph with.
Powder type as a major axis,
like we're not talking about the powder
type,
like we're gonna talk about the powder
doser, the powder doser, and I like that,
yeah,
I agree that something can be combined,
so if you go to the hospital, but...
Nothing flows on its own.
15 second static hold with no actuation
produced no mass change.
One exception.
Silicon.
Would you agree with that?
Across every powder and every tilt,
a 15-second static hold with no actuation.
Produce no mass change.
Does it mean that it cleared its own runs
in this? Ohh, OK,
just like it's not a button, yeah.
Yeah, OK.
Clean shut off.
One to 12% of a revolution.
I guess one thing we didn't do,
if we really wanted to get into the fine
details of here, is if we had a pause,
what happens if we pause it here?
So one revolution, pause and go again,
or like pause it half a revolution.
That would kind of resolve the...
Like, what's happening, yeah, yeah,
what's happening inside the auger, yeah,
yeah, transparent augers, yeah,
that we got a bunch would be awesome,
yeah, technically we do the resin prints,
yeah, they have some very transparent,
yeah, ones,
chat about you need to cure inside.
Yeah, that's right. Yeah, that would be,
then it's tacky. Yeah, those are so tacky.
It is with, yeah,
probably for most things. Okay,
nothing flows on its own.
The tap is a fine increment.
A firmware defect, the EDA turned up.
Tune, yeah, turned up. Is this okay?
Are you okay going through? Yeah,
this still? Okay. Yeah.
Block D over rotates by a factor that
stepped mid-campaign.
Actual commanded rotation.
From.
Interesting. It's saying on August 13th.
to August 19th.
It.
Rotated more.
Than it used to.
For the same.
Oh my, when it commands one, oh,
it commanded 3 revolutions,
and the actual was...
A little bit more than that prior to that.
But then, at some point,
it started really overdoing the the
revolution rotation.
The week of August 13th,
somewhere between August 13th and August
19th, 20th.
You're saying that's like a factor of
like the funeral or something? Yeah.
There's gonna be a loose thing I don't
know.
Let's do this.
True.
Maybe I'll put this.
Where is this from?
Speirs.
I don't know how long we've been live
streaming for.
I forget when we set up the, like,
start to have the, yeah,
the powder does for live stream stuff.
You know,
you need to know where she started.
Then I think I'll put this one.
Uhh...
What?
And.
OK, this one.
Okay,
and then it's saying when I corrected it.
Then...
Makes more sense.
It makes more sense for milligrams per
revolution. Okay.
One thing I had to keep forgetting to
change this: it thinks that the stepping
motor and the auger gear are the same
ratio, and specifically,
there have been a couple of times they
ask you, like, what's the ratio?
And it's like one to one. It's really not.
So I need to just let that,
let her know that and I can update the
data. Okay. Oh, gotcha.
That'll affect all the,
everything that says revolution. Right.
When I put command in three revolutions,
that was one revolution.
Ohh, well, OK, maybe I don't know, yeah,
like,
and it could be inconsistent with where
sometimes it's accounting for that,
and other times it's, yeah,
so you need to let it know that it's,
yeah, there is a difference there, yeah.
There were no change in parts, right?
I don't think there were any like parts
swap outs, yeah.
Mhm.
Yeah, sure.
Which parameter explains the rate at our
identity? OK,
so this is kind of going for a...
A little bit of a feature importance. Yes,
sure. Powder affects it a lot.
Tilt angle has a high effect.
Powder and tilt interaction.
Not as much as what I'm saying.
What does that mean as opposed to like?
I think it's saying which knob
specifically is doing this and what's the
interaction. Yeah, so yeah,
I wouldn't have split that up.
So it'll show sometimes things like this,
it'll show both.
Split up just individually,
and then also show cross-correlations
with, yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
Nested decomposition of log 10 milligrams
per revolution over all resolvable block
C revolutions, saying that I think, yeah,
I know kind of no powder identity there,
so kind of all I care about.
The rest, um,
and I care more about like the tilt
interaction with the other ones. Yeah,
I think was covered some other places,
yeah, a little bit.
This is a reasonable, yeah,
like randomize the order, yeah.
All faster book.
I was hoping for something a little more.
Far bit of them.
Yes.
Yeah.
If you were to go back and collect some
more data, going back to...
This,
if we had an H and an I that was like 100
milligrams.
I don't know, you do like.
Yeah, like 50 milligrams, 200 milligrams,
1 gram.
I don't know if we want to go up to like
the 5 grams because we're going to have
to be rebuilding it. It'll be a lot.
I think.
I don't even know if we have 5 grams to
send this. I know, yeah, exactly. So.
Which, yeah, if we're going to redo,
or not redo,
but do you know which ones are pretty
limited on?
This one of them is a really small bottle.
Do you know which one, which one?
It's not the fume silica,
it's the sorry sulfate,
the this is silicon,
I think it's silicon 102 and ohh, OK,
yeah, I gotcha, yeah, yeah, so.
Best.
Yeah, if we added an H and an I.
Where H is.
Oh.
5200 and 1000.
feels kind of okay for capturing
different ranges.
It doesn't capture the University of Utah.
Range quite as well,
but it's I just don't know.
If we're going to...
Like,
and it's in the fume hood for a lot of
these,
and there's maybe like a 50 milligram
noise threshold on some of it,
so in some sense it's a little safer to
go with a little higher,
given the fume hood stuff. What,
what do they need to be?
What point do they need to be dispensing
it? Do you? Ohh, I think it's, yeah,
I'm trying to remember, it was...
So they can be smaller than that? Yeah,
like on the like 1 milligram.
I think it's...
Ohh.
Can the current system reliably deliver 0.
1 to 10 milligrams of the powder to a
small reaction vial or 96 well played? No.
Yeah.
And I think we could probe that more.
So, first off,
I think we want more of Will stuff in
place,
where before we spend a whole bunch of
time, yeah, yeah, I want that,
and then second,
I think we would want really good
vibration isolation, yeah, for it,
and third, probably new auger.
Like dimensions, yeah, the dimensions,
yeah,
'cause I think it'll be too hard to do
when you change the dimensions, yeah,
yeah, yeah, you know.
Yeah. And the error. Yes.
So, I think...
I think 50 milligrams is already kind of
a...
No, like, for the noise, or like, like,
we're only gonna be able to say so much
about the, yeah, yeah, the noise.
At some point, did you introduce that? Or,
I guess, like,
it might be worth trying to differentiate,
and this could just be in supplementary
information.
when it was in the fume hood,
when it was in the lab,
like our lab space,
and when the box went over it.
Which we might be able to get from,
I mean, Claude, I think we probably, yeah,
do that from the live streams.
The box was only a few second. Ohh, OK.
OK, that's easy on that one, and I think..
.
All of the food safe powders were in the
lab, yeah,
and all of the non-food safe were in the
feedback, yeah, yeah,
I'll let it know that for sure.
I think it does know, but yeah, but...
Yeah.
Spring back some memories.
Which did you see made the new design?
I watched the video, yeah, I like it,
I like it a lot, yeah, yeah,
it's still got a ways to go,
but it's something, yeah,
I really like that, you know,
and it brought, I brought the idea too,
and...
Maybe useful to have a weighing station
as well.
And you could come in,
we could weigh it somehow with like a,
I don't know, like right now it like a...
Oh, I see. Yeah.
There's something like they could push it
up and then they check the weight of that
and then it can dispense and then go back
and check the weight again. Yeah.
But I guess you just put a load cell on
the... Yeah.
On the end of it, probably, yeah,
and it is like attached to the engines,
like that's something that, like,
it's not like it's the full weight of it
is, oh yeah, you'd have to correct for it,
yeah, but the raw data, OK.
You can put a current measurement, yeah,
yeah, like there's some ways to get it.
I think,
I think a load cell would probably be the,
yeah, most straightforward, but I'm like,
no, I just want to measure the signal,
like I don't want to have to redesign,
yeah, like a load cell, yeah,
but that one might not be too bad,
maybe too bad.
I like that idea. Yes, it's cool. Yeah,
see the answers in here.
Yeah, so...
This is a lot of graphs. Yeah.
Do you want to cut this down a bit? Like,
I'll run some more tests and stuff.
I'm a little anxious to get this out
there. Yeah, I'm with you. The,
especially like ideally if you can get it
back with revisions. Yeah.
More like November would be awesome, yeah,
and...
I think I can do these tests this week.
Yeah, hopefully, not tomorrow at Thursday,
and then...
Yeah.
So, I guess, do you wanna,
are there any of these that you're like,
put this in,
or should we run the test and then meet
again and talk? Ohh, right, right,
the extra test.
I think we should try to get it mostly
finalized,
where all we're doing is just adding,
like filling in some of that.
What do you think about the 50 and the 50
milligrams and the 200 milligrams?
We could wait.
Like one, we could just say,
maybe the reviewers come back with that
as a request and we say, okay, done. Yeah.
If it's a couple months, then.
We'll have to factor in the the powder
will have been sitting for, well,
actually.
We could submit it,
we could run those tests because we care
about it and it'll, yeah,
affect things for Will as well to have
that as a baseline,
like one way or another,
I think we will collect that, yeah, data.
This is if we do it before or after, like,
submit the paper, yeah, so I'm...
It could.
We're also going to put the preprint out
there. So yeah,
and I think that would be a strength for
the preprint as people are looking at the
preprint. Yeah, to say like.
It's a natural question they want to be
asking.
You can kind of infer it based on all the
other parameters that are done. It's like,
back to that question. Well,
if I want 50 milligrams, can I get it?
And how long does it take?
And how accurately did it get to that?
I'll run it on Thursday. Yeah, OK.
And, like, this in downtime, too,
so I can, okay, listen,
so then you gave me this list of, like,
we need graphs to show, like,
unique powder type and the one, like,
which ones load best and how accurate,
and maybe the time to get to do this
point, how accurately you did that,
and that kind of thing.
And enjoying for like.
What's the best way to get the graphs
into the paper? Should we have,
should we like make this list of graphs
that we want to graph that shows this
versus this, this versus this,
this versus this, or should we...
Like, I'm a little overwhelmed with, like,
we have a lot of graphs here, yeah,
and requiring a lot of changes,
so I'm wondering if I should just say,
like, make a list of, like, we want these,
yeah, 8 figures, give, like,
look at the data and give me these eight
figures or something like that.
I'll take the transcription recording,
I'll have it try to summarize that,
if you could also send that to me, yeah,
so I can include that in the prompt.
Yeah, so then we'll review the...
The finalized the prompt that comes from
our prompt, yeah,
so you have it right in the prompt to do
graphs, more graphs, yeah,
we'll take the transcript,
we'll take your notes, yeah,
we'll have Claude merge that into a...
cohesive set of things.
We'll double check it.
I think then we'll just let it run. Yeah.
I'll send this to you and then we'll have
it do that once I've run these new tests
so that it can include that data as well.
We can do that now.
Like we'll do all this now,
but then when the new data comes in,
we'll just say, hey,
here's this new today.
Sweet.
And then after that, I think...
It might make sense for...
you to do a similar process and maybe
with Will and Luke involved too of...
If you're open to it,
what I talked about with the tensegrity
project of screen record, start to finish,
just through it, tear it apart, yeah,
tear it apart.
Collect that from everybody.
Update it, do a couple iterations,
and I think that sometimes it's not until
the 3rd iteration that you get like some
good, yeah, you've probably noticed,
sometimes it, yeah, yeah,
when you get it just the right amount
after a couple passes, it can be, yeah,
at least I think it would be good enough
to say.
Okay, thank you. Yeah,
we're just gonna bring this into Overleaf.
We'll make any final edits, and then yeah,
here's the PDF, then we'll submit. Yeah,
that sounds good to me,
so that I feel like I have a good plan
for how we're gonna get the graphs and
how we're gonna get the paper. Okay, yeah.
Sounds good. That's good.
And I just really got to say, you...
You ran 1200 experiments.
That's pretty cool. That's amazing.
That's pretty cool.
And most of it was automated,
like I ran in these batches of like, yeah,
like we ran like 13 patterns, I think.
Yeah. And out of those,
like each of those, I guess,
was about 100 trials. Yeah. So, and I,
yeah. That's really cool.
That's pretty cool. Like, yeah.
Regardless of.
Like the life of the projects, yeah,
compared to that, too, yeah, yeah,
like if you were spending all of your
time just collecting that data, yeah,
you still probably wouldn't be, yeah,
you might not be able to get to the, yeah,
like the full 1200, yeah.
Maybe, but there's a lot, right?
There's a lot, yeah, and I think you, I,
I feel pretty common saying,
I don't think you would enjoy the work as
much as if you were,
if all you did in the lab was like,
it doesn't care, like,
let me dose this in another way, yeah.
How fast can I do this? Yeah,
it'll be okay. Awesome.
Thanks for taking this. Yeah, 2 hours.
Yeah, yeah,
that's what for the semester now.
I think I can do about 10 hours a week.
Great.
And the, yeah, and give me a heads up if..
.
Um...
Yeah, how things are going,
like if that still seems manageable, yeah,
yeah, for you, yeah,
some weeks I know it will be, yeah,
fluctuate, yeah, yeah,
and trying to get this out as soon as
possible, and then, yeah, that's good.
And, and for this semester,
trying to get the multi-doser after this
is out, yeah,
getting multi-doser up and running, yeah,
so.
Which looks like it's really,
I think the concept is really there.
You already have the prototype with the,
yeah, the unit.
I think there's a couple of, yeah,
couple of units to work out, but yeah,
awesome. Thank you.
Yeah, and I'll send this list to you.
Did you send that now-ish? Yes,
'cause we'll probably do that right after.
Just, yeah, let me, yeah,
I'll just do it right now.